Tell us that there is no God for them.
There was a first commit threat by Satan.
But I don't know if the first time they have confused, they do not know.
They are not sure about the hereafter.
So they are not feeling secure about the hereafter.
So they have to rely on something else that can protect them.
They can give them the security they want.
that can give them the guarantee for a position they're going to have in the hereafter.
And the people who are chasing the last time, they're telling them to be
well, they're not in the state, they're just by following Satan.
That my Satan wants to provide the believers, the group, the family of the believers.
They fall into this trap and these are the gossippers or whatever.
They are talking about each other.
Now I am coming again to the origin of something about the Bible.
And now as I was saying, I am going to call these verses to the first part.
So the four scriptures I am saying, there is no difference between them.
And they all say the same thing was the wonder.
Your God is one.
But the Christians unfortunately,
they followed the purpose of Satan.
And Satan, this is not that he's done
into making them at his.
So he put them, he made them out of his.
Or he divided them.
And they say he's God or some of God.
You can see each other
[ Silence ]